Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
This blade has a dark past.
It has shed much innocent blood.
You're a fool for traveling alone,
so completely unprepared.
You're lucky your blood's still flowing.
Thank you.
So...
What brings you to
the land of the gatekeepers?
I'm searching for someone.
Someone very dear?
A kindred spirit?
A dragon.
A dangerous quest for a lone hunter.
I've been alone for
as long as I can remember.
We're almost done. Shhh...
Hey, sit still.
Good night, Scales.
Get him, Scales! Come on!
Scales?
Yeah! Come on!
Scales!
I have failed.
You've only failed to see...
These are dragon lands, Sintel.
You are closer than you know.
Scales!
Scales?
Scales...
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/f93t
Help other users to choose the best subtitles